[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MR. SONG] (In Korean)
Just find the necklace.
It will lead you
to my daughter.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Get her DNA to confirm.
What is that for?
What's that?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Chairman Song...
sent me to find a necklace.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's yours.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
He thought it would lead to
looking for his lost daughter.
And it did.
He wants to meet you, Hannah.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No wonder
they're so mad at me.
But, uh, my job...
My job as a translator...
What's that?
I just needed an excuse...
to stay close to you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
So, it's all fake?
The clothes,
your concern...
You were just pretending?
You just wanted
to get to know me?
The chairman wants proof...
that you're his daughter.
You should've just asked.
You should've just asked me.
I will tell the truth.
I'm here.
Yes.
I am the chairman's daughter.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC INTENSIFIES]